<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="aon-chase.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Denman Chase | Cheltenham Gold Cup Trial Races | Result | Odds | Newbury | Betting]]></title><keys><![CDATA[denman chase, cheltenham gold cup trial races, result, odds, newbury, free bets, betting, history, winner, denman, form guide, betfar]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the result and form for the 2014 Denman Chase at Newbury which is a key trial race for the Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Trials - Denman Chase</h1>
<p>
	The Aon Chase offers Gold Cup horses with one last chance to get a good run in falling as it does in February of each year at Newbury, nevertheless it has turned into a worthy trial to the Gold Cup since its first running in 2000. It can offer those horses that need a tune up ready for the big race the perfect opportunity to have a run out in competitive company after Christmas.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Cheltenham Gold Cup 2014 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	In recent years both Kauto Star in 2007 and Denman in 2008 won the Aon Chase before heading to Cheltenham the following month to pick up the Gold Cup, which only serves to highlight the potential importance of this race to punters having a Gold Cup bet. As well as Gold Cup horses we may well see one or two runners in the Denman field that maybe heading towards Aintree and a tilt at the Grand National at the start of April.</p>
<p>
	We shall be following the race in 2014 as always so punters will be able to track the form of all the major runners just a month or so ahead of the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">2014 Gold Cup</a>.</p>
<h2>
	Denman Chase Result</h2>
<div>
	<strong>14:25 Betfair Denman Chase (3m) (Grade 2)</strong></div>
<div>
	1.Harry Topper - K Baiiley - J Maguire - 7/2</div>
<div>
	2.Al Ferof - P Nicholls - D Jacob - 5/4F</div>
<div>
	5 Ran</div>
<h2>
	Past Winners of the Aon Chase</h2>
<ul>
	<li>
		2013 - Silviniaco Conti</li>
	<li>
		2012 - Long Run</li>
	<li>
		2011 - Noland</li>
	<li>
		2010 - Tricky Trickster</li>
	<li>
		2009 - Madison Du Berlais</li>
	<li>
		2008 - Denman</li>
	<li>
		2007 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>
		2006 - No Race</li>
	<li>
		2005 - Farmer Jack</li>
	<li>
		2004 - Shooting Light</li>
	<li>
		2003 - Valley Henry</li>
	<li>
		2002 - Bacchanal</li>
	<li>
		2001 - Shotgun Willy</li>
	<li>
		2000 - See More Business</li>
</ul>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>