<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="arkle-trophy.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Arkle Trophy Odds | Cheltenham Festival 2015 | Betting | Runners | Races]]></title><keys><![CDATA[arkle trophy odds, cheltenham festival 2015, betting, runners, races, form, contenders, favourite, trainers, connections, gold cup]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the odds and betting for the 2015 Arkle Chase which is one of the feature races on the first day of the Cheltenham Festival.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 1 Races - Arkle Trophy Odds</h1>

<p>The Arkle Trophy is the second race on the Day 1 card at the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festival</a> and it is a race that of course is named after the legendary chaser, it is one of the most popular races for up and coming chasers over the 2 mile distance.</p>

<p>We have had some cracking winners of the race in recent years with Forpadydeplasterer winning in 2009 Sizing Europe in 2010 just two of the notable names on the roll of honour. A number of nice horses are running this year including <strong>Un De Sceaux</strong> who has been very impressive so far this season for Willie Mullins.</p>

<h2>Arkle Chase Result 2015</h2>

<p>14:05 Racing Post Arkle Challenge Trophy Chase (Grade 1)<br />
1.Un De Sceaux - W Mullins - R Walsh - 4/6F<br />
2.God's Own - T George - P Brennan - 33/1<br />
3.Josses Hill - N Henderson - B Geraghty - 12/1<br />
11 Ran</p>

<h2>Arkle Chase Result 2014 - Click To Bet</h2>

<p><strong>14:05 Racing Post Arkle Challenge Trophy Chase (Grade 1)</strong><br />
1.Western Warhorse - D Pipe - T Scudamore - 33/1<br />
2.Champagne Fever - W Mullins - R Walsh - 11/4JF<br />
3.Trifolium - C Byrnes - B Cooper - 11/4JF<br />
9 Ran</p>

<h2>2013 Result</h2>

<p><strong>2:40 Racing Post Arkle Challenge Trophy Chase Grade 1 Cl1 2m</strong><br />
1. <strong>Simonsig</strong> - B J Geraghty - N J Henderson 8/15 Fav<br />
2. <strong>Baily Green</strong> - D J Casey - M F Morris 33/1<br />
3. <strong>His Excellency</strong> - T Scudamore - D Pipe 80/1<br />
7 Ran</p>

<h2>2012 Result</h2>

<p><strong>14:05 Racing Post Arkle Challenge Trophy Chase (Grade 1) (5yo+, Class 1, 2m)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Sprinter Sacre</strong> (B J Geraghty) 8/11Fav<br />
2. <strong>Cue Card (J Tizzard)  13/2</strong><br />
6 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>