<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="betfair-chase.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Betfair Chase | Cheltenham Gold Cup Trial Races | Result | Form | Odds | Haydock]]></title><keys><![CDATA[betfair chase, cheltenham gold cup trial races, result, form, odds, haydock, long run, winners, imperial commander]]></keys><description><![CDATA[The Betfair Chase is a key Gold Cup Trial race at Haydock Park and will feature Long Run who won the Gold Cup in 2013.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Trial Races - Betfair Chase 2013</h1>
<p>
	The Betfair Chase is a young race but one that is growing in stature with every passing season, it is the first Grade 1 race of the season in the UK and attracts the very cream of the crop as they make their seasonal debuts at Haydock Park. It has only been run since 2005 but the great Kauto Star has taken the honours three times so far, including in 2009 when he held off a charge from Imperial Commander in a titanic battle. It served as a great Gold Cup trial race as it turned out with Imperial Commander getting his revenge at Cheltenham to claim his first Gold Cup victory.</p>
<p>
	The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting</a> will be adjusted after this race with current favourite <strong>Bobs Worth</strong> set to make his seasonal debut at Haydock. He could well face <strong>Silviniaco Conti</strong> though who is a top class horse on his best day, the Paul Nicholls horse fell in the Gold Cup last season but could still be anything.</p>
<h2>
	Betfair Chase Result 2013</h2>
<div>
	<strong>15:00 Betfair Chase (Registered As The Lancashire Chase) (Grade 1)</strong></div>
<div>
	1.Cue Card - C Tizzard - J Tizzard - 9/1</div>
<div>
	2.Dynaste - D Pipe - T Scudamore - 11/2</div>
<div>
	3.Silviniaco Conti - P Nicholls - N Fehily - 7/2</div>
<div>
	8 Ran</div>
<h2>
	Betfair Chase Roll Of Honour</h2>
<ul>
	<li>
		2005 - Kingscliff</li>
	<li>
		2006 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>
		2007 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>
		2008 - Snoopy Loopy</li>
	<li>
		2009 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>
		2010 - Imperial Commander</li>
	<li>
		2011 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>
		2012 - Silviniaco Conti</li>
</ul>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>