<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="bets.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Gold Cup Bets 2014 | Betting Markets and Specials]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cheltenham gold cup bets, odds, special betting, without favourite, each-way, markets]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the different betting options for the 2014 Cheltenham Gold Cup including each betting and Special bets]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Bets 2014</h1>
<p>
	Outside of the Grand National the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> is the biggest single betting race of the National Hunt season with any number of different markets on offer for punters, from the straight forward win market to the various types of novelty bets there really is something for everyone. The race this year could be tighter than ever with the old guard of Denman, Kauto Star and Imperial Commander clashing with the likes of Long Run and What A Friend who could be the future of the race.</p>
<h2>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting Options</h2>
<p>
	The main bet for punters is always the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Outright Win Odds</a> and that is no different for the 2011 Gold Cup, it is the most straight forward and simple bet on offer and this year we are seeing Kauto Star and Imperial Commander heading this market. Punters can choose to have a bet on which horse they believe will win the race or for a lower risk option they can have an each-way punt. When having a bet each-way then the horse will need to finish in the top three to pay out, this of course increases the chances of winning but at the same time reduces the potential value of the winnings.</p>
<p>
	Outside of the main bets there are a number of other bets for punters to get involved with at the Gold Cup, one of those is to follow the Champion Trainer Paul Nicholls in the race. In recent years the the Ditcheat Trainer made the Gold Cup his own with Kauto Star and Denman dominating between 2007 and 2009, they will both be back in 2011 along with a number of other stable stars from Nicholls. Other potential runners from Nicholls this season include the likes of What a Friend and Neptune Collonges so the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/paul-nicholls-specials.html">Paul Nicholls Special Bets</a> are always worth taking a close look at.</p>
<p>
	At the moment we have two warm favourites heading the betting in Bobs Worth and Sir Des Champs, the rest of the field are at a longer price making the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-without-big-two.html">Betting Without The Big Two</a> an attractive market. This could of course all change as the season progresses but if they remain the ones to beat punters should have a look at this one; it is a market that assumes the top two in the betting will come home first and second in the Gold Cup. So in affect punters are betting on the horse they believe will finish third in the race, this will of course give them a nice chance of winning but at the same time the odds of the horse will be significantly reduced.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>