<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="bobs-worth.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Bobs Worth Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders Form And Betting]]></title><keys><![CDATA[bobs worth odds, cheltenham gold cup betting 2014, form, runners, festival, nicky henderson, season, races, jockeys, connections, contender, prices, market]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and form for Bobs Worth who is one of the leading contenders in the betting for the 2014 Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders 2014 - Bobs Worth</h1>
<p>
	Bobs Worth is another potential <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> runner in 2013 for Nicky Henderson after a brilliant past couple of years. The horse has won at the Cheltenham Festival for the past two years and the natural progression will see him joining Gold Cup company ahead of the 2013 renewal. In 2011 we saw Bobs Worth arrive on the big stage when he won the Albert Bartlett Hurdle at the Festival and he has been marked out as a horse to watch ever since. Henderson already has a Gold Cup winner in his yard in the form of Long Run and it will be fascinating to see how Bobs Worth matches up if the pair meet in the near future.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Current Bobs Worth Cheltenham Gold Cup 2014 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	In 2012 we saw Bobs Worth go chasing and he duly confirmed his talent at Cheltenham once again as he won the RSA Chase at the Festival. That run confirmed his ability to stay and his love for jumping which should make him a live Gold Cup contender at a course he clearly thrives at. Barry Geraghty seems to have a great relationship with Bobs Worth and the pair of them always seem to produce when it matters as they did when beating First Lieutenant into second place in the RSA Chase.</p>
<h2>
	Bobs Worth Gold Cup 2013 Form</h2>
<p>
	Bobs Worth made his seasonal debut at Newbury in the Hennessy Gold Cup and he started as a warm favourite. The Henderson horse had plenty of weight to carry after his exploits last season but he travelled really well and pulled clear when asked to do so to claim an excellent win. It was a very pleasing return for Bobs Worth in testing conditions and he continued his unbeaten run going left handed with the bookmakers slashing his price for the Gold Cup as a result.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>