<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="burton-port.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Burton Port Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 | Runners | Betting | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[burton point odds, cheltenham gold cup 2013, runners, betting, form, chances, free bets, henderson, races]]></keys><description><![CDATA[Burton Port is a potential runner in the 2013 Gold Cup at Cheltenham and features his latest form and betting odds for the race.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2013 - Burton Port</h1>
<p>
	Burton Port is not a household name even in some horse racing circles but he is real contender for the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">2013 Cheltenham Gold Cup</a>, the Nicky Henderson horse is still young but is full of class as he has shown in recent years. He slowly improved and stepped up in class last season and is expected to join Gold Cup company over the coming weeks and months. Nicky Henderson has long been confident of his ability at the top level and he will have his chance to back that up soon enough, at the moment he is not one of the favourites for the big race but at the same time the bookmakers will be watching his progress very closely.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Burton Port Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	At the back end of last season we saw Burton Port winning the Mildmay Novice Chase at Aintree in good company, he showed his potential that day and caught the eye of many ahead of a Gold cup tilt this season. He also ran a good race at the Cheltenham festival in March behind Weapons Amnesty in the RSA Chase, the natural progression from the RSA is the Gold Cup and it was a good performance from the young horse. That day he defeated the hugely talented <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/long-run.html">Long Run</a> who himself could be set for a run in the Gold Cup in March.</p>
<p>
	Burton Port certainly has shown the potential to be a star but at this stage we are waiting to see if he fulfils that ability this season, it is guess work at the moment so we like the punters will be watching his early season form with some considerable interest.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>