<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="captain-chris.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Captain Chris Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders 2013 | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[captain chris odds, cheltenham gold cup contenders 2013, form, betting, connections, trainer, jockey, richard johnson]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and form for Captain Chris who is one of the leading contenders in the betting for the Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders 2013 - Captain Chris</h1>
<p>
	Captain Chris is a hugely consistent and popular horse who is right on track for a tilt at the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> this season. The Philip Hobbs horse has been mixing it at the top level for a good couple of years now with his win in the 2011 Arkle Chase at Cheltenham more than proof of that fact. That win saw him beat Finains Rainbow into second place and we know that he has of course gone onto win the Queen Mother Champion Chase which makes that form rock solid.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Current Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting Price for Captain Chris</a></p>
<p>
	Following his Arkle win Captain Chris went through a period of jumping out to his right which looked set to ruin his chances of winning another big race but slowly he has come back to his best. Last season we saw Captain Chris finish a staying fourth in the Ryanair Chase and that signalled something of a return to form for the horse. He has carried that progression on this season with a good win at Ascot in the Amlin Chase and then perhaps a career best second place in the King George at Kempton on Boxing Day.</p>
<p>
	The King George is always one of the highest class races of the season and that was certainly the case in 2012 when Captain Chris ran a blinder. Under a good ride from Richard Johnson the horse was held up at the rear before picking the horses off one by one over the final mile or so to confirm his stamina on heavy ground. At the last it looked as though Captain Chris was going to win only for him to be worn down on the line by 2011 Gold Cup winner <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/long-run.html">Long Run</a>.</p>
<p>
	Connections were clearly very pleased with the run from Captain Chris at the King George and the Gold Cup is now the clear plan. There has to be question marks about his chances of winning the race against the likes of Bobs Worth and Sir Des Champs but he is not without a chance of running into a place. We know he acts on soft ground as he has shown this season which punters should take note of and at a big price he could offer some nice each-way value.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>