<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="champion-bumper.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Champion Bumper Odds | Cheltenham Festival 2015 | Races | Betting | Runners]]></title><keys><![CDATA[champion bumper odds, cheltenham festival 2015, races, betting, runners, form guide, free bets, chances, flat race, national hunt]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the latest betting and runners for the 2015 Champion Bumper at the Cheltenham Festival, the race is for juveniles and run over the flat under National Hunt rules.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 2 - Champion Bumper Odds</h1>

<p>The Champion Bumper is the most unique race of the entire <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festival</a> in the fact that there are no obstacles for the horses to jump, it is run under National Hunt rules for the juvenile horses and often gives us the chance to see the stars of the future. The Champion Bumper itself has not been around for too long but already it is one of the highlights of the meeting as the final race on the day 2 card of the Festival.</p>

<p>In recent years we have had some fantastic winners of the Champion Bumper with the likes of Cousin Vinny and Dunguib starting off their careers with a huge victory at the Festival, while Champagne Fever is another top class recent winner.</p>

<h2>Champion Bumper</h2>

<p><strong>17:15 Weatherbys Champion Bumper (Grade 1 Standard Open NH Flat Race)</strong><br />
1.Moon Racer - D Pipe - T Scudamore - 9/2F<br />
2.Modus - R Stephens - T O'Brien - 33/1<br />
3.Wait For Me - P Hobbs - R Johnson - 9/1<br />
24 Ran</p>

<h2>2013 Result</h2>

<p><strong>5:15 Weatherbys Champion Bumper (A Standard Open National Hunt Flat Race) Grade 1 Cl1 2m110y</strong><br />
1. <strong>Briar Hill</strong> - R Walsh - W P Mullins 25/1<br />
2. <strong>Regal Encore</strong> - A P McCoy - A Honeyball 7/1 JF<br />
3. <strong>Golantilla</strong> - D E Mullins - A J Martin 9/1<br />
4. <strong>The Liquidator</strong> - T Scudamore - D Pipe 16/1<br />
23 Ran</p>

<h2>2012 Result</h2>

<p><strong>17:15 Weatherbys Champion Bumper (Grade 1 Standard Open NH Flat Race) (Class 1, 2m 110y)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Champagne Fever</strong> (Mr P W Mullins) 16/1<br />
2. <strong>New Year's Eve (B J Geraghty) 9/2Fav</strong><br />
3. <strong>Pique Sous</strong> (R Walsh) 12/1<br />
20 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>