<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="cheltenham-festival.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Festival 2015 | Gold Cup | Races | Schedule | Dates ]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cheltenham festival 2015, gold cup, races, schedule, date, odds, betting, days, champion hurdle, champion chase, day 1, wednesday, world hurdle, novices, handicap]]></keys><description><![CDATA[The Cheltenham Festival is the premier race meeting of the season with 27 races over four days, featuring all the betting and form for each of the races.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival - 10th-13th March 2015</h1>

<p>The Cheltenham Festival is quite simply the highlight of the National Hunt season in the UK and Ireland, it is what everyone works towards during the winter with the Cheltenham Festival affectively holding the Championship races every March. The Festival itself is held over four days and continues to expand with every passing season, each of the four days has a feature race with the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup </a>on Day Four the feature race of the meeting.</p>

<p>It is a huge week for the whole racing industry with punters at the centre of the attention, the betting for each race often rights right through the season and up until seconds before the off. The bookmakers had a great week at Cheltenham in 2010 with many of the favourites upset during the four days, the punters though will be out for revenge as always with 27 races on offer. The Festival covers races for every tpe of horse whether it be for the Juveniles in the Champion Bumper or the Mares in the David Nicholson Hurdle there really is something for everyone at the Festival.</p>

<p>The biggest betting of the week of course surrounds the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Gold Cup Odds</a>, with the top three mile chasers around clashing for the big prize of the year. The Champion Hurdle is the key race on Day 1 with the very best two mile hurdles clashing, while the big race on day 2 is the Queen Champion Chase over the bigger obstacles. The Champion Chase will be hugely competitive in 2015 with the likes of Sprinter Sacree and Sire De Grugy set to lock horns, the betting is looking tight here so their early season form will be crucial.</p>

<p>Day 3 sees the staying hurdlers take centre stage with the Ladbrokes World Hurdle the feature race of the day, Big Buck&#39;s will be back in 2014 and likely to be the hot favourite for a fifth win in the race for the Paul Nicholls yard.</p>

<h2>Cheltenham Festival Races/Schedule 2015</h2>

<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/day-1.html"><strong>Cheltenham Festival Day 1</strong></a></p>

<ul>
	<li>Supreme Novices Hurdle</li>
	<li>Arkle Challenge Trophy</li>
	<li>Festival Handicap Chase</li>
	<li>Champion Hurdle</li>
	<li>David Nicholson Mares Hurdle</li>
	<li>National Hunt Chase</li>
	<li>Centenary Novices Chase</li>
</ul>

<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/day-2.html"><strong>Cheltenham Festival Day 2</strong></a></p>

<ul>
	<li>Neptune Investment Novices Hurdle</li>
	<li>RSA Chase</li>
	<li>Coral Cup</li>
	<li>Queen Mother Champion Chase</li>
	<li>Cross Country Chase</li>
	<li>Fred Winter Handicap Hurdle</li>
	<li>Champion Bumper</li>
</ul>

<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/day-3.html"><strong>Cheltenham Festival Day 3</strong></a></p>

<ul>
	<li>JLT Novices Chase</li>
	<li>Pertemps Final Handicap</li>
	<li>Ryanair Chase</li>
	<li>Ladbrokes World Hurdle</li>
	<li>Byrne Group Plate</li>
	<li>Kim Muir Challenge Cup</li>
</ul>

<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/day-4.html"><strong>Cheltenham Festival Day 4</strong></a></p>

<ul>
	<li>JCB Triumph Hurdle</li>
	<li>County Handicap Hurdle</li>
	<li>Albert Bartlett Novices Hurdle</li>
	<li>Cheltenham Gold Cup</li>
	<li>Foxhunter Chase</li>
	<li>Conditional Jockeys Hurdle</li>
	<li>Grand Annual Chase</li>
</ul>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>