<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="conditional-jockeys-hurdle.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Conditional Jockeys Hurdle Odds | Cheltenham Festival 2014 | Betting | Races | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[conditional jockeys hurdle odds, cheltenham festival 2014, betting, races, form, free bets, favourite, contenders, young jockeys]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and race information for the 2014 Conditional Jockeys Hurdle at the Cheltenham Festival.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 4 Races - Conditional Jockeys Hurdle Odds</h1>

<p>The Conditional Jockeys get their chance on the big stage with this excellent hurdle race, it really is a chance for the young jockeys to have their moment in the sun and a good ride could really give their careers a boost. The race itself is run over 2 miles 4 furlongs so at middles distance the weather could play a part here, it is one of the final races of the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festival</a> though and punters are always eager to get involved.</p>

<p>We have had a few runnings of the race so far but generally the bookmakers have come out on top, in 2009 it was Andytown who won at 25/1 while in 2011 it was Pause And Clause who scored at 14/1.</p>

<p><strong>16:40 Martin Pipe Conditional Jockeys' Handicap Hurdle</strong><br />
1.Killultagh Vic - W Mullins - L Dempsey - 7/1<br />
2.Noble Endeavour - G Elliott - K Sexton - 14/1<br />
3.Roi Des Francs - W Mullins - D Mullins - 3/1F<br />
4.Kauto Grand Mogul - Miss E Doyle - J McGarvey - 33/1<br />
24 Ran</p>

<h2>Conditional Jockeys Hurdle Result 2014</h2>

<p><strong>16:40 Martin Pipe Conditional Jockeys' Handicap Hurdle</strong><br />
1.Don Poli - W Mullins - Mr P Fogarty - 12/1<br />
2.Thomas Crapper - R Dickin - J Palmowski - 10/1<br />
3.Caid Du Berlais - P Nicholls - H Derham - 9/1<br />
4.Urbain De Sivola - P Nicholls - A Guerin - 33/1<br />
24 Ran</p>

<p><strong>16:40 Martin Pipe Conditional Jockeys' Handicap Hurdle (Class 2, 2m 4f 110y)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Attaglance (Harry Haynes) 20/1</strong><br />
2. <strong>Toner D'Oudairies</strong> (K M Donoghue) 7/1<br />
3. <strong>Oscar Nominee</strong> (D Bass) 10/1<br />
4. <strong>Make A Track</strong> (B R Dalton) 12/1<br />
24 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>