<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="cooldine-.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cooldine Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2011 | Runners | Betting | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cooldine odds, cheltenham gold cup 2011, runners, betting, form, chances, free bets, willie mullins]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and form for Cooldine who is one of the leading contenders for the 2011 Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2011 - Cooldine</h1>
<p>Cooldine is yet another Irish Raider who will be looking to head over the Irish Sea to take in the Cheltenham Gold Cup, the Willie Mullins horse has proven himself to be a hugely consistent performer over the last year and should not be ruled out here. Cooldine made his mark on racing at the 2009 <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festiva</a>l when he hosed up in stunning style to win the RSA Chase. Ever since then he has been ear marked for success but has failed to win since, he has had some decent efforts though including a respectable 5th place in the Gold Cup back in March.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Cooldine Cheltenham Gold Cup 2011 Betting Odds</a></p>
<p>He never really troubled the leaders that day which is a worry but he stayed on well and kept to his task, he is also coming into his prime at nine so should be one to keep an eye on this season. Willie Mullins was unable to get him out before Christmas last season which could have caused him a problem so he is sure to start him off early if possible this campaign. He did improve gradually last season with his third place in the Guinness Gold Cup perhaps the highlight of his season at the Punchestown Festival, he is rarely out of the places in Group 1 company so will attract plenty of each-way money.</p>
<p>On all form last season he looks to be slightly below the level needed to win the Gold Cup so will need to improve, Cooldine does enjoy Cheltenham though as he showed in 2009 so will be aimed at another <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> tilt this season.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Cooldine 2010/11 Form</h2>
<p>Cooldine started his season with a solid if unspectatcular run in the John Durkan Memorial Chase at Fairyhouse, he went off well backed and despite staying on well he could only manage a 5th place finish. Willie Mullins will be hoping he comes on for the run but on this form he will struggle in the Gold Cup against the bigger guns.</p>]]></content><articles></articles></page>