<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="cross-country-handicap.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cross Country Handicap Odds | Cheltenham Festival Runners And Betting]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cross country handicap odds, cheltenham festival 2015, runners, betting, races, form guide,  favourite, contenders, prices]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting for the Cross Country Handicap at the Cheltenham Festival, as well as the form for the leading contenders.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 2 - Cross Country Handicap Odds</h1>

<p>The Cross Country Handicap is like no other Festival race as the field take in all manner of obstacles both on the race course and in the middle of the course, this race really tests the navigational skills of the jockeys as they wind and turn their way around the course. As well as the usual fences we have grass banks, water jumps and Aintree fences for the Cross Country runners to deal with, this is what makes the race so special for fans and punters alike at the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festival</a>.</p>

<p>In recent years the Irish have had something of a stranglehold on the Cross Country race with trainer Enda Bolger in particular holding a great record in the race, he has saddled four winners of the race including Garde Champetre who won in 2008 and 2009.</p>

<h2>Cross Country Chase Result</h2>

<p><strong>16:00 Glenfarclas Handicap Chase (Cross Country)</strong><br />
1.Rivage D'Or - A Martin - D Russell - 16/1<br />
2.Any Currency - M Keighley - A Coleman - 7/1<br />
3.Uncle Junior - W Mullins - Mr P Mullins - 20/1<br />
4.Dogora - W Mullina - Ms K Walsh - 20/1<br />
16 Ran</p>

<h2>Cross Country Chase Result 2014</h2>

<p><strong>16:00 Glenfarclas Handicap Chase (Cross Country)</strong><br />
1.Balthazar King - P Hobbs - R Johnson - 4/1<br />
2.Any Currency - M Keighley - I Popham - 10/1<br />
3.Big Shu - P Maher - P Carberry - 3/1F<br />
4.Duke of Lucca - P Hobbs - T O'Brien - 25/1<br />
16 Ran</p>

<h2>2012 Result</h2>

<p><strong>16:00 Glenfarclas Handicap Chase (Cross Country) (5yo+, Class 2, 3m 7f)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Balthazar King</strong> (R Johnson) 11/2<br />
2. <strong>A New Story</strong> A P Heskin) 20/1<br />
3. <strong>Wedger Pardy</strong> (Miss J Coward)  33/1<br />
4. <strong>Garde Champetre</strong> (Miss N Carberry) 5/1<br />
16 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>