<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="cue-card.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cue Card | Cheltenham Gold Cup Odds 2014 | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cue card, cheltenham gold cup odds 2014, form, contenders, price, betting, joe tizzard]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the latest betting and form for Cue Card who is a leading contender for the 2014 Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cue Card - Cheltenham Gold Cup Odds 2014</h1>
<p>
	One of the more interesting potential Gold Cup runners this season is the excellent Cue Card who could well take his chance for Colin Tizzard. The eight-year-old has proven himself to be one of the best horses in training over the past few years and many believe that he is a genuine <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net">Gold Cup</a> horse. He burst onto the scene back in 2010 when he stormed clear of the field to win the Champion Bumper at the Festival and he has been improving ever since.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Cue Card 2014 Cheltenham Gold Cup Win Odds</a></p>
<p>
	Since that victory, Cue Card has been right among the best chasers in the sport with his Ryanair Chase victory in 2013 another clear highlight. that day he was popped out in front in his customary fashion and he was simply too good for the likes of First Lieutenant and Riverside Theatre among others. Connections have long believed that Cu Card would suit three miles and he finally proved that theory earlier this season when he stormed to a memorable win in the Betfair Chase at Haydock Park.</p>
<p>
	Cue Card dispatched the likes of Bobs Worth, Dynaste and Silviniaco Conti in great style to produce a career best performance. That immediately sparked off talk of a Gold Cup win and a repeat of that run at the Festival would see him right in the mix in March. There are however still one or two doubts surrounding his stamina, especially if the ground comes up testing at the Festival.</p>
<p>
	The Colin Tizzard horse started the King George on Boxing Day as a hot favourite but after leading for much of the race, he tired into second place behind Silviniaco Conti. He looked the winner all over two out from home but he suddenly looked tired coming to the last and he was out-stayed in the end in testing conditions which does put his Gold Cup hopes in the balance.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>