<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="day-2.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Festival Day 2 | Wednesday Betting |  Card and Races]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cheltenham festival day 2, wednesday, races, champion chase, card, rsa chase, 2015, bumper]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the race sand betting for day 2 of the 2015 Cheltenham Festival including the Queen Mother champion Chase and the Champion Bumper]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival 2015 Day 2 - Ladies Day</h1>

<p>Day 2 picks up where Day 1 left off with some great racing, the opener on Wednesday is the National Hunt Steeple Chase where the amateur Jockeys get their chance to shine at the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festival</a>. It is a tough race for Novice Chasers and they must be able to stay the trip as the likes of Tricky Trickster and Poker De Sivola have shown in the past couple of years.</p>

<p>The Neptune Investment Novices Hurdle is next up on the card on Wednesday and it is another race that continues to grow in stature and importance, it is run over 2 m 5f so often attracts potential staying hurdlers of the future. Peddlers Cross was hugely impressive in winning for Donald McCain Jnr last season, he is one who is expected to excel this season so the Neptune can be a vital race for a young star. The RSA Chase has grown into a feature race in its own right over the past couple of year's, it really is one of the highlights on the card from a betting point of view. The RSA Chase can be used as a stepping stone towards a Gold Cup tilt as Denman proved by winning the race in 2007 followed by the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> itself in 2008.</p>

<p>The features race on Day 2 is of course the Queen Mother Champion Chase for 2 mile chasers, it never fails to excite on the track and in the betting ring with some great value always on offer for punters. The best in the class meet and we have had some great winners down the years, in recent times we have seen Sizing Europe win in 2011 while Big Zeb won in style in 2010. All being well those two will be locking horns once again in 2013 in another clash of the titans, the betting will run all season with Sprinter Sacre the one to beat at the moment.</p>

<p>The Coral Cup is somewhat of a lottery with such a big field at the tape, at the same time though it does make it all the more interesting for the spectators and punters with value on offer right through the market. Following the Coral Cup is the Fred Winter Handicap for the Juvenile Horses aged four, you often get some nice improving types in the field meaning there is quite often a nice price winner of the race. The final race of the day is the all important Champion Bumper which is of course a flat race run under National Hunt Rules, this is a chance for trainers to get their superstars of the future out at Cheltenham ahead of a Novice Hurdling Campaign the following year. Recent impressive winners of the Bumper include the likes of Dunguib and Cue Card who have since turned into real star names.</p>

<h2>Cheltenham Festival Day 2 Card</h2>

<ul>
	<li><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/neptune-novices-hurdle.html">Neptune Investment Hurdle</a></li>
	<li><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/rsa-chase.html">RSA Chase</a></li>
	<li><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/coral-cup.html">Coral Cup</a></li>
	<li><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/queen-mother-champion-chase.html">Queen Mother Champion Chase</a></li>
	<li><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cross-country-handicap.html">Cross Country Chase</a></li>
	<li><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/fred-winter-handicap-hurdle.html">Fred Winter Handicap Hurdle</a></li>
	<li><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/champion-bumper.html">Champion Bumper</a></li>
</ul>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>