<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="denman.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Denman Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup Odds 2012 | Form | Runners | Betting]]></title><keys><![CDATA[denman odds, cheltenham gold cup odds 2012, form, runners, betting, chances, the tank, free bets, winner, nicholls]]></keys><description><![CDATA[The form and betting for Denman who is one of the leading contenders for the 2012 Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2012 - Denman</h1>
<p>
	Denman is a horse that has won the hearts of the nation over the past four or five years with some extraordinary performances to his name, the highlight of his career so far was his brilliant Gold Cup win in 2008 at Cheltenham. His run that day was sensational as he galloped a top class field into the ground including his great rival Kauto Star to claim a memorable win.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Denman Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	It is clear that Denman is slightly past his best but his run in the 2012 Gold Cup behind Long Run has to be given the respect it deserves, he does seem to save his best runs for Cheltenham and if he can produce a strong gallop the rest of the field will find it tough to leave with the pace. Denman does throw in the odd bad race these days but he has the knack of bouncing back in the big races, his weight carrying victory in the 2009 <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/hennessy-gold-cup.html">Hennessy Gold Cup</a> was simply sensational at a time when most had written The Tank off.</p>
<p>
	He will be 12 by the time <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">the Gold Cup</a> comes around in March which may count against him but he will come in for plenty of money from punters, he is sure to offer good each-way value and should be watched closely. It may be a little too much to ask of Denman to win another Gold cup in 2012 at the age of 12 but he rarely runs a bad race at the Festival and has to be given the respect he deserves.</p>
<p>
	Paul Nicholls has said that Denman will start his season off with a run in the Lexus Chase over Christmas where he will be in tip top shape. A good run there will see him confirmed for Cheltenham and he will then go straight there after the Lexus if he can stay fit and fresh.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>