<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="diamond-harry.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Diamond Harry Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 | Form Guide | Betting | Runners]]></title><keys><![CDATA[diamond harry odds, cheltenham gold cup 2012, form guide, betting, runners, free bets, hennessy winner, chances, nick williams]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and form guide for Diamond Harry who is one of the leading contenders for the 2012 Cheltenham Gold Cup]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2012 - Diamond Harry</h1>
<p>
	Diamond Harry could be a real <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> contender for 2012 if he has regained his best form which saw him winning the Hennessy gold cup at Newbury back in 2010. That win was top class and although he has been injured since he still looks to be a progressive chaser. Harry had his first run since that Hennessy win recently when he ran in the Betfair Chase at Haydock, he ran a solid race but never looked like winning to finish fourth. The Ian Williams horse is lightly raced over fences which means he should improve this season but he remains fragile and still has to prove himself off of level weights in Gold Cup level.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Diamond Harry Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	He has shown over the years that he is a class type with many wins to his name while his two runs at the Cheltenham Festival would have to be a slight worry for his ante post backers. He came third in the Ballymore Novices Hurdle back in 2009 behind Mikael D&#39;haguenet and Karabak while he was pulled up in the RSA Chase in 2010, that would be a worry and he will need to overcome those Cheltenhm troubles if he is to mix&nbsp; it with the likes of Long Run and Kauto Star.</p>
<p>
	Diamond Harry looked much improved at Newbury for the Hennessy last season with his jumping in particular looking much better, if he can continue that form through this season then he is very much one to watch and that is reflected in the latest betting.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>