<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="flemenstar.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Flemenstar Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2013 | Form Guide | Contenders]]></title><keys><![CDATA[flemenstar odds, cheltenham gold cup runners 2013, form guide, contenders, peter casey, connections, trainer, races]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and latest form for Flemenstar who is one of the leading contenders in the Cheltenham Gold Cup Market for the Festival.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2013 - Flemenstar</h1>
<p>
	One new name to emerge onto the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net">Gold Cup</a> scene this season is the highly progressive Flemenstar. The Peter Casey trained star has been sweeping all before him in Ireland over the past year or two and he looks set to take his chance in the Gold Cup for the first in March. Last season connections decided to swerve Cheltenham but all roads lead to Prestbury Park this time around if he remains fit and well.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Flemenstar Cheltenham Gold Cup Win Odds</a></p>
<p>
	He started to come to the fore last season over in Ireland as he put together a fine winning streak and that has continued once again this campaign. His first start this season was at Navan in the Fortria Chase over two miles and he swept aside former Champion Chaser Big Zeb in some style. That was a fine run considering the trip and he improved even more more next time out in the John Durkan Chase at Punchestown.</p>
<p>
	That run at Punchestown placed him against the previously unbeaten over fences Sir Des Champs over 2m4f with most considering the two of them to be the best staying chasers in Ireland. In the end though there was only one winner as Flemenstar streaked away to produce a career best performance which saw his Gold Cup price slashed for March.</p>
<p>
	Connections are convinced that Flemenstar is a stayer although he is yet to be tested over three miles. That examination is likely to come in the Lexus Chase over Christmas against Sir Des Champs once again and if he can repeat his John Durkan win over further he will really be a Gold Cup contender. He could well be the star of the Festival if he continues to improve while his trainer Peter Casey is one one of the more colour characters of the sport making Flemenstar a horse to follow this season.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>