<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="foxhunter-chase.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Foxhunter Chase Odds | Cheltenham Festival 2014 | Races | Betting | Runners]]></title><keys><![CDATA[foxhunter chase odds, cheltenham festival 2014, races, betting, runners, free bets, favourite, contenders, amateur gold cup]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and race news for the Foxunter Chase at the 2014 Cheltenham festival, won in 2013 by Salsify.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 4 Races - Foxhunter Chase Odds</h1>

<p>The Foxhunter Chase is often referred to as the 'Amateur Gold Cup' as it is run over the same course and distance as the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a>, the only difference being the quality of the field as well as the Jockeys who are all amateur riders. The horses in this field will have had to qualify through the season either in hunter chases of point-to-point chases.</p>

<p>Despite not being a race of the highest quality it is always a competitive race both on the track and in the betting rings and as punters try their best to pick the winner, last season we saw Salsify to the victory on a great day for the yard. The betting for this one tends to only be released during the week of the Cheltenham Festival so be sure to keep an eye on this page over the coming weeks and months.</p>

<p>16:00 St. James's Place Foxhunter Chase Challenge Cup<br />
1.On The Fringe - E Bolger - Ms N Carberry - 6/1<br />
2.Following Dreams - A Ralph - S Drinkwater - 50/1<br />
3.Paint The Clouds - W Greatrex - Mr S Waley-Cohen - 11/4f<br />
4.Carsonstown Boy - C McBratney - Mr N McParlan - 11/1<br />
24 Ran</p>

<h2>Foxhunter Chase Result 2014</h2>

<p><strong>16:00 CGA Foxhunter Chase Challenge Cup</strong><br />
1.Tammys Hill - L Lennon - Mr J Smyth - 15/2<br />
2.Carsonstown Boy - C McBratney - Mr N McParlan - 40/1<br />
3.On the Fringe - E Bolger - N Carberry - 11/2<br />
24 Ran</p>

<p><strong>16:00 Christie's Foxhunter Chase Challenge Cup (Class 2, 3m 2f 110y)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Salsify</strong> (Mr C J Sweeney) 7/1<br />
2. <strong>Chapoturgeon</strong> (Mr J Barber) 3/1Fav<br />
3. <strong>Oscar Delta</strong> (Mr D Murphy) 28/1<br />
22 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>