<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="grand-annual.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Grand Annual Odds | Cheltenham Festival 2014 | Betting | Runners | Races]]></title><keys><![CDATA[grand annual odds, cheltenham festival 2014, betting, runners, races, form guide, free bets, favourite, contenders]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and race information for the 2014 Grand Annual at the Cheltenham Festival.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 4 Races - Grand Annual Odds</h1>

<p>We now come to the final race of the entire week and the Grand Annual Chase, this is a race for the more average chaser but it gives them and connections the chance to have a winner at <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">the Cheltenham Festival</a>. In 2010 we saw Pigeon Island cap a wonderful day for Nigel Twiston-Davies following Imperial Commander's win in the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> earlier on.</p>

<p>Punters will be looking for one last chance to get one over on the bookmakers in the Grand Annual so expect plenty of activity on the betting front; it has proved tough though with only one favourite winning the race since St Pirran in 2004. </p>

<p><strong>17:15 A.P. McCoy Grand Annual Handicap Chase (For The Johnny Henderson Challenge Cup) (Grade 3)</strong><br />
1.Next Sensation - M Scudamore - T Scudamore - 16/1<br />
2.Eastlake - J O'Neill - P Carberry - 12/1<br />
3.Croco Bay - B Case - K Woods - 14/1<br />
4.Ned Buntline - N Meade - AP McCoy - 4/1JF<br />
20 Ran</p>

<p></p>

<h2>Grand Annual Result 2014</h2>

<p><strong>17:15 Johnny Henderson Grand Annual Chase Challenge Cup (Grade 3 Handicap)</strong><br />
1.Savello - A Martin - D Russell - 16/1<br />
2.Ned Buntline - N Meade - P Carberry - 6/1JF<br />
3.Claret Cloak - E Lavelle - N Fehily - 6/1JF<br />
4.Next Sensation - M Scudamore - R Johnson - 7/1<br />
24 Ran</p>

<p><strong>17:15 Johnny Henderson Grand Annual Chase Challenge Cup (Grade 3 Handicap) (Class 1, 2m 110y)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Bellvano</strong> (P Carberry) 20/1<br />
2. <strong>Tanks For That</strong> (B J Geraghty) 9/1<br />
3. <strong>Kumbeshwar (R Thornton) 16/1</strong><br />
4. <strong>Anquetta</strong> (A Tinkler)  33/1<br />
21 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>