<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="imperial-commander.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Imperial Commander Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 | Runners | Form | Betting]]></title><keys><![CDATA[imperial commander odds, cheltenham gold cup 2013, runners, form, betting, chances, 2010 winner, twiston-davies, jockey, bets, free bets, ]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the form and betting for Imperial Commander who will be looking to win the 2013 Cheltenham Gold Cup for Nigel Twiston-Davies.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2013 - Imperial Commander</h1>
<p>
	Imperial Commander upset the odds in 2010 to simply blow away the field at Cheltenham to win the Gold Cup, Nigel Twiston-Davies had been telling anyone that would listen that his horse would win and he duly obliged at a nice looking 7/1. He is a brilliant horse that seems to come into his own at Cheltenham with some great course form under his belt, as well as his win in <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">the Gold Cup</a> he also won the Ryanair Chase at the Festival in 2009.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Imperial Commander Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	Imperial Commander went head-to-head with Denman over the final few furlongs and came out on top to highlight his class, there was no beating Imperial Commander on the day as he once again relished running at Prestbury Park. With Paddy Brennan on board Imperial Commander stormed clear of Denman and if he can reproduce that form in 2011 he will be tough to beat once again. He is a horse that is often difficult to judge as he does tend to save his best form for Cheltenham, he has run two woeful races in the King George at Kempton in recent years before going to the Festival and winning in style meaning his form through the season does need to taken with a pinch of salt.</p>
<p>
	This season we will see Imperial Commander take his tried and tested route to the Festival with the Betfair Chase at Haydock set to be his first appearance, before he heads to Kempton again on Boxing Day for the King George with the hope of getting ready for the defence of his Gold Cup defence. Much will be made of his form when we see him in the Betfair as we see him for the first time since falling at Aintree in the Totesport Bowl in April. It will be hoped that his confidence has not been knocked by that slip up and time will tell if he can join the<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/legends.html"> Gold Cup legends</a> and claim a second victory in the race.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/race-card.html">Full Gold Cup Racecard</a></p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>