<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="index.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Gold Cup - Odds Betting and Runners]]></title><keys><![CDATA[2016 cheltenham gold cup, tips, runners, odds comparison, form, bookmakers, online betting, festival, horse racing, goldcup, betfred]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and odds for the Cheltenham Gold Cup which is a key race at the Cheltenham Festival.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting</h1>

<p><img alt="Cheltenham Gold Cup Denman" src="images/denman.jpg" style="float:right" /></p>

<p>The Mark Bradstock trained Coneygree was the brilliant winner of the Gold Cup last season but he will unfortunately miss the defence of his title after picking up an injury which means the race is wide open.</p>

<p>Another key <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/race-card.html">Gold Cup Runner</a> in March could well be <strong>Vautour </strong>who is being stepped up in trip this season with this race in mind. He was sensational when winning the JLT Novices Chase at the Festival for Willie Mullins and in terms of class, it is hard to ignore his claims</p>

<p>It is also well worth keeping an eye on <strong>Don Cossack</strong> who was the highest rated chaser in training last season for Gordon Elliott and he is likely to be among the favourites in the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Gold Cup Odds</a> when the tapes go up in March.</p>

<h2>Cheltenham Gold Cup Guide 2016</h2>

<p>On this site we provide you with the best information to assist you in making that bet as we will have all the information on the 2016 Cheltenham Gold Cup runners for the race along with the best odds and form. Make sure you also check out our <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/tips.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup tips</a>, along with the best Gold Cup free bets from some of the top bookmakers.</p>

<p>It really has been a golden era for the Gold Cup over the past few years with the likes of Kauto Star, Denman and Long Run claiming memorable wins in the big race. The rivalries between the big names and trainers have served to boost the popularity of the race and that looks set to continue in 2016. The current hero is of course Coneygree who claimed a famous win in 2015 for Mark Bradstock and he is sure to be well backed again next season.</p>

<p>See <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/form-guide.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Form Guide</a> for the background and performances of the main contenders for the 2016 Gold Cup including Bobs Worth and Silviniaco Conti among others.</p>

<h2>Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners and Riders</h2>

<p>The best chasers of the season will head to Cheltenham for the showpiece Gold Cup and all the connections of the well fancied horses will be looking to get the bets jockeys for their horses. The final list of 2015 <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/runners.html">Gold Cup Runners </a> will not be known until the 48 hour stage but we can expect to see the likes of Coneygree and Coneygree to head the field.</p>

<p>Other potential runners in the big race in 2016 include the talented Don Poli who was the winner of the RSA Chase, while Saphir Du Rheu is tipped for a big season this year in Gold Cup company and could be a major player.</p>

<h2>Gold Cup Trial Races 2016</h2>

<p>There is a tried and tested route towards the Gold Cup for all of the main contenders in the betting and we will be following each of them through the season. 2012 winner Synchronised went over to Ireland at Christmas to win the Lexus Chase before heading to Cheltenham and that race in particular is always one to watch. Perhaps the most prestigious of the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/trials.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Trials</a> is the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/king-george-vi-chase.html">King George VI Chase</a> at Kempton on Boxing Day. Over the past few years we have seen both Kauto Star and Long Run win on Boxing Day before going to Cheltenham to win the Gold Cup and no doubt we will see a number of Festival hopefuls take their chance once again this season.</p>

<p>Punters will be able to follow all of the big races right through until the Gold Cup itself in March to help them make sense of a competitive betting heat, the last big trial race in February is the Denman Chase at Newbury and that will be the last chance for connections to get a run into their Gold Cup hopefuls.</p>

<h2>Choosing your Gold Cup Online bookmaker</h2>

<p><img alt="Cheltenham Festival Gold Cup" src="images/cheltenham_festival.jpg" style="float:right" />The other sections on this site will hopefully have helped you with your Gold Cup selection. To assist you in selecting an online bookmaker, we have put up the very best online bookmakers for your perusal most of which you will be familar with. The selection of bookmakers shown on this site are all amongst the very best in the UK and Ireland and all offer quality racing services and the choice can just come down to the price that they are offering for your selection in the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting Odds</a>. There will be differences between the online bookmakers on the price and this is because each will have different liabilities on the race and therefore there are slight differences in the prices offered. You might also like to check out our section on <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/opening-an-online-betting-account.html">opening an online betting account</a>.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>