<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="jewson-novice-chase.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[JLT Novice Chase Odds | Cheltenham Festival | Betting | Runners | Races]]></title><keys><![CDATA[jlt novice chase odds, cheltenham festival, betting, runners, races, free bets, new race, favourite, contenders]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and race information for the JLT Novice Chase at the Cheltenham festival, including the latest odds for the race.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 3 Races - JLT Novice Chase Odds</h1>

<p>The JLT Novices Chase is still a newish to the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festival</a> and it is already popular with racegers at the Festival, it is a 2mile 5 furlong race for novice chasers and should attract a high quality field. It will be the first race on day 3 at the Festival and its distance ensures it will fall in between the 2 mile Arkle and the 3 mile RSA Chase, so will be ideal for the horses who would have previously struggled in either of those renewals.</p>

<p>There had been some worries that this new race would dilute the quality of races like the Arkle and RSA Chase, but at this stage those fears appear to be unfounded with some classy types lining up in each of the races.</p>

<h2>JLT Novices Chase Odds - Click to Bet</h2>

<p><strong>13:30 JLT Novices' Chase (Registered As The Golden Miller Novices' Chase) (Grade 1)</strong><br />
1.Vautour - W Mullins - R Walsh - 6/4f<br />
2.Apache Stronghold - N Meade - P Carberry - 7/1<br />
3.Valseur Lido - W Mullins - B Cooper - 9/2<br />
8 Ran</p>

<h2>JLT Novices Chase Result</h2>

<p><strong>13:30 JLT Novices' Chase (Registered As The Golden Miller Novices' Chase) (Grade 1)</strong><br />
1.Taquin Du Seuil - J O'Neill - AP McCoy - 7/1<br />
2.Uxizandre - A King - R Thornton - 33/1<br />
3.Double Ross - N Twiston-Davies - S Twiston-Davies - 11/1<br />
12 Ran</p>

<p><strong>13:30 Jewson Novices' Chase (Registered As The Golden Miller Novices' Chase) (Grade 2) (Class 1, 2m 4f)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Sir Des Champs</strong> (D N Russell) 3/1<br />
2. <strong>Champion Court</strong> (A P Cawley) 8/1<br />
3. <strong>For Non Stop</strong> (N Fehily) 8/1<br />
10 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>