<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="kauto-star-v-denman.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Kauto Star v Denman | 2011 Cheltenham Gold Cup | Betting | Odds]]></title><keys><![CDATA[kauto star v denman, 2011 cheltenham gold cup, betting, odds, free bets, paul nicholls, part III, special bet, ap mccoy, ruby walsh]]></keys><description><![CDATA[Kauto Star v Denman for the Cheltenham Gold Cup including the latest betting and form of each horse.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Kauto Star v Denman - Cheltenham Gold Cup 2010</h1>
<p>There is one sporting clash that everyone is talking about at the moment and that is the clash between the two best horses of a generation at this years Cheltenham Gold Cup, its Kauto Star v Denman Part III and this year promises to be the best of the lot with both in cracking form. It is set to be the race of the ages as it may just be that the two will meet on top form for the very first time and punters are split as to which way the big race will go.</p>
<p>Kauto Star won the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> in 2007 in fine style&nbsp;when Denman was not in the race, they first met in the 2008&nbsp;Gold Cup and it was Denman who produced a simply stunning performance to blow away Kauto and the rest of the field. 2009 saw the rematch but this time it was Kauto Star who became the first horse ever to regain the Gold Cup with a dominant performance, Denman came in a good second after a tough season with a heart problem. That means that the current score stands at 1-1 and we are all set for the decider at Cheltenham in March, both have been in sparkling form this season and both connections are full of confidence.</p>
<h2>VCBet Free £125 on the 2010 Gold Cup</h2>
<p><a target="_blank" href="out.php?url=10"><img alt="" align="right" border="0" src="http://www.moneta-communications.com/banners/vcbet/vcbet_125x100.gif" /></a>VCBet better known as Victor Chandler is a leader in online betting with online punters. Victor is a real old fashioned bookmaker and he enjoys laying a decent bet. They are offering a £125 FREE Bet on&nbsp;the 2010 Gold Cup&nbsp;for new customers using their online sportsbook and have created a simple account opening system to make this FREE Bet possible. Just follow the links on this page</p>
<p><a target="_blank" href="out.php?url=10">Open an account with VCBet and claim £125 Gold Cup&nbsp;Free Bet</a></p>
<p>Kauto Star picked up his 4th successive King George Chase win at Kempton on boxing Day to prove his form while Denman blew away the field when carrying top weight in the Hennessy gold Cup back in November meaning they both look in good shape. Paul Nicholls is the lucky trainer who looks after both horses and publicly at least he will not split the horses, Denman has recieved a boost recently with the news that AP McCoy will take the ride in the Gold Cup while Ruby Walsh has&nbsp;stayed loyal to&nbsp;Kauto Star. It looks as though Kauto Star will go into the race as the slight favourite in the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Odds</a> with Denman not far behind, one thing is for sure and that is&nbsp;barring any incidents they will be the first two home on March 19th.</p>]]></content><articles></articles></page>