<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="kauto-star.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Kauto Star Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 | Betting | Runners | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[kauto star odds, cheltenham gold cup 2012, betting, runners, form, free bets, chances, nicholls, winner, prestbury park, denman, record, ruby walsh]]></keys><description><![CDATA[Kauto Star is one of the leading contenders for the 2012 Cheltenham gold Cup and includes his latest form and betting for the big race.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2012 - Kauto Star</h1>
<p>
	Over the past five years Kauto Star has proven himself to be a superstar chaser and he will be going for his third Gold Cup victory in 2012, the Paul Nicholls horse has been supremely consistent during his career so far and few would be surprised to see him have another great season. Kauto Star won the Gold Cup in 2007 and 2009 both times in some style, along with that he has won the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/king-george-vi-chase.html">King George Chase</a> at Kempton four times and while he is clearly past his best he is still capable of running a massive race.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Kauto Star Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	Kauto Star shocked the racing world in November when he won the Betfair Chase in brilliant style to role back the years. Many had called for connections to retire him but he simply blew away a field including Long Run and Weird Al who are both likely <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> opponents in March. That performance immediately put paid to talk of retirement as he jumped with such enthusiasm to gallop his rivals into the ground, if he can stay at that level he will remain a massive Gold Cup threat this season.</p>
<p>
	Kauto Star has followed that win in the Betfair Chase with an equally impressive win in the King George Chase at Kempton. He once again galloped from the front to run Long Run off his feet on Boxing Day. Long Run was forced into jumping mistakes by Kauto Star to the delight of the crowd and the Gold Cup now looks a fascinating race between the big two. It was a fifth win in the King George for Kauto Star and whatever happens at Cheltenham he will be remembered as a legend of the sport.</p>
<p>
	At the moment we are waiting to hear if Kauto Star will make the Gold Cup at Cheltenham after the horse suffered a fall at home recently. Paul Nicholls has said that Kauto is no more than 50/50 to line up at the Festival and plenty of punters and racing fans will be keeping their fingers crossed.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>