<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="kim-muir-challenge-cup.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Kim Muir Challenge Cup Odds | Cheltenham Festival 2015 | Betting | Runners | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[kim muir challenge cup odds, cheltenham festival 2015, betting, runners, form guide, races, free bets, favourite, contenders]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the odds and betting for the Kim Muir Challenge at the 2015 Cheltenham Festival]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Day 3 Races - Kim Muir Challenge Cup Odds</h1>

<p>The Kim Muir Challenge Cup is on Day 3 of the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">2015 Cheltenham Festival</a> and it is another race on the card for the amateur jockeys, it gives these jockeys a chance to shine at the big Festival and it is always a competitive race for the punters to sink their teeth into. It is run just over 3 miles on the New Course at Prestbury Park and was first run in 1946, it is always worth looking out for the top amateur jockeys in this race with some of them working with the top trainers.</p>

<p>Recently we have had some classy winners of the race with the likes of Cloudy Lane, Character Building and Ballabriggs who won for Donald McCain Jnr lin 2011. There can be some excellent value for punters here, and the market will be available closer to the race right here.</p>

<h2>Kim Muir Odds - Click To Bet</h2>

<p><strong>16:40 Fulke Walwyn Kim Muir Challenge Cup Handicap Chase (Amateur Riders)</strong><br />
1.The Package - D Pipe - Mr J Codd - 9/1<br />
2.Bless the Wings - G Elliott - N Carberry - 28/1<br />
3.Buddy Bolero - A Martin - Mr  K Power - 20/1<br />
4.Grand Vision - C Tizzard - Mr M Legg - 11/1<br />
24 Ran</p>

<h2>Kim Muir Result 2014</h2>

<p><strong>16:40 Fulke Walwyn Kim Muir Challenge Cup Handicap Chase (Amateur Riders)</strong><br />
1.Spring Heeled - J Culloty - Mr R McNamara - 12/1<br />
2.Cause Of Causes - G Elliott - N Carberry - 13/2<br />
3.Roberto Goldback - N Henderson - Mr S Waley-Cohen - 16/1<br />
4.Balnaslow - W Mullins - Mr P Mullins - 9/1<br />
23 Ran</p>

<p><strong>16:40 Fulke Walwyn Kim Muir Challenge Cup Handicap Chase (Amateur Riders) (Class 2, 3m 1f 110y)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Sunnyhillboy</strong> (Mr A J Berry) 13/2Fav<br />
2. <strong>Becauseicouldntsee</strong> (Mr R P McNamara) 9/1<br />
3. <strong>Exmoor Ranger (Mr J Guerriero) 33/1</strong><br />
4. <strong>Up The Beat (Mr P W Mullins) 8/1</strong><br />
23 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>