<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="king-george-vi-chase.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[King George VI Chase | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2014 | Trial Races | Result | Form | Odds]]></title><keys><![CDATA[king george vi chase, cheltenham gold cup 2014, trial races, result, kauto star, history, roll of honour, kempton, boxing day, odds, betting, bets]]></keys><description><![CDATA[The full result and odds for the the 2014 King George VI Chase at Kempton Park, which is a trial race for the Gold Cup at Cheltenham in March.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Gold Cup Trial Races - King George VI Chase</h1>

<p>There is no doubt that the most prestigious Gold Cup Trial of them all is the King George VI Chase at Kempton Park, the Boxing Day race is a huge renewal in its own right but also gives punters some crucial clues ahead of the Gold Cup. The race at Kempton takes places just under three months before the Gold Cup so is a very popular race with trainers as they look to get a good run into their horses ahead of the Cheltenham Festival. The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Gold Cup Odds</a> will be adjusted drastically after the King George so it does have a big affect for the ante post Gold Cup punters.</p>

<p>Over the history of the King George there are two names that stand out on the roll of honour, they are the great Desert Orchid who won the race four times and of course Kauto Star who won on no less than five occasions.</p>

<h2>King George VI Chase Odds - Click To Bet</h2>

<p>#%(showOdds, king-george-vi-chase-2014)%#</p>

<h2>King George VI Chase Roll Of Honour</h2>

<ul>
	<li>2013 - Silviniaco Conti</li>
	<li>2012 - Long Run</li>
	<li>2011 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>2010 - Long Run</li>
	<li>2009 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>2008 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>2007 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>2006 - Kauto Star</li>
	<li>2005 - Kicking King</li>
	<li>2004 - Kicking King</li>
	<li>2003 - Edredon Bleu</li>
	<li>2002 - Best Mate</li>
	<li>2001 - Florida Pearl</li>
	<li>2000 - First Gold</li>
	<li>1999 - See More Business</li>
</ul>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>