<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="lexus-chase.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Lexus Chase Betting | Cheltenham Gold Cup Trial Races | Result | Odds | History | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[lexus chase, cheltenham gold cup trial races, result, odds, history, free bets, betting, leopardstown, form, runners]]></keys><description><![CDATA[A full review and reuslt of the Lexus Chase at Leopardstown which is a key trial race for the Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Trial Races - Lexus Chase Betting</h1>
<p>
	The Lexus Chase is perhaps the premier Gold Cup Trial race over in Ireland through the season, this ensures that there is always an outstanding field at Leopardstown for the race and punters should watch the race closely. The recent list of winners is highly impressive with both Irish and British winners of the race, they include the likes of Denman and Best Mate who both went onto win the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> during the same season.</p>
<p>
	There will always be one or two runners in the Lexus who head across the Irish Sea from the UK to take on the grade 1 race, this is due to the fact with its Christmas running it provides the ideal time frame ahead of a Gold Cup run. It clashes very much with the King George Chase at Kempton which is also a crucial trial race for the Gold Cup so more often than not you will see both fields jam packed with top class entries. Each of the two races will give plenty of pointers for punters as well as the bookmakers who will be watching both Leopardstown and Kempton with some interest over the Christmas period.</p>
<h2>
	Lexus Chase Result 2013</h2>
<div>
	14:55 Lexus Chase (Grade 1)</div>
<div>
	1.Bobs Worth - N Henderson - B Geraghty - 11/4jf</div>
<div>
	2.First Liutenant - M Morris - D Casey - 7/1</div>
<div>
	3.Rubi Ball - W Mullins - D Russell - 8/1</div>
<div>
	9 Ran</div>
<h2>
	Recent Winners of the Lexus Chase</h2>
<ul>
	<li>
		2012 - Tidal Bay</li>
	<li>
		2011 - Synchronised*</li>
	<li>
		2010 - Pandorama</li>
	<li>
		2009 - What A Friend</li>
	<li>
		2008 - Exotic Dancer</li>
	<li>
		2007 - Denman*</li>
	<li>
		2006 - The Listener</li>
	<li>
		2005 - Beef Or Salmon</li>
	<li>
		2004 - Beef Or Salmon</li>
	<li>
		2003 - Best Mate*</li>
	<li>
		2002 - Beef Or Salmon</li>
	<li>
		2001 - Foxchapel King</li>
	<li>
		2000 - Rince Ri</li>
</ul>
<p>
	*Went onto win the Cheltenham Gold Cup in the same season</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>