<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="national-hunt-steeple-chase.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[National Hunt Steeple Chase Odds | Cheltenham Festival 2015 | Runners | Betting | Races]]></title><keys><![CDATA[national hunt steeple chase odds, cheltenham festival 2015, runners, betting, races, free bets, favourite, contenders]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and race information for the 2015 National Hunt Steeple Chase at the Cheltenham Festival.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Races Day 1 - National Hunt Steeple Chase Odds</h1>

<p>One of the day 1 <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham</a> races is the National Hunt Steeple Chase and is for novice chasers, it is the longest race at the Festival with the runners taking on a stamina sapping 4 mile trip around the Old Course. It is also a race for amateur jockeys who are always looking to make the most of their chance at the Festival, there will be a big field for punters to pick over as they look to start day 2 with a bang.</p>

<p>We have had some nice winners of the National Hunt Chase in recent years with the likes of Teaforthree and Back In Focus scoring over the past few years, both of them have gone onto bigger things since.</p>

<h2>National Hunt Chase esult 2015</h2>

<p><strong>16:40 Toby Balding National Hunt Chase (Listed Amateur Riders' Novices' Chase)</strong><br />
1.Cause Of Causes - G Elliott - Mr J J Codd - 8/1<br />
2.Broadway Buffalo - D Pipe - Ms K Walsh - 12/1<br />
3.The Job Is Right - M Hourigan - Mr D O'Connor - 10/1<br />
17 Ran</p>

<h2>National Hunt Chase Result 2014</h2>

<p><strong>16:40 Terry Biddlecombe National Hunt Chase (Listed Amateur Riders' Novices' Chase)</strong><br />
1.Midnight Prayer - A King - Mr J Newman - 8/1<br />
2.Shotgun Paddy - E Lavelle - Mr D O'Connor - 7/2<br />
3.Suntiep - W Mullins - Mr P Mulins - 9/1<br />
15 Ran</p>

<p><strong>1:30 John Oaksey National Hunt Chase (Amateur Riders´ Novices´ Chase</strong><strong>) Cl2 4m</strong><br />
1. <strong>Back In Focus</strong> - Mr P W Mullins - W P Mullins 9/4 Fav<br />
2. <strong>Tofino Bay</strong> - Ms N Carberry - D T Hughes 8/1<br />
3. <strong>Godsmejudge</strong> - Mr N De Boinville - A King 7/1<br />
16 Ran</p>

<h2>2012 Result</h2>

<p><strong>13:30 Diamond Jubilee National Hunt Chase (Amateur Riders' Novices' Chase) (Class 2, 4m)</strong><br />
1. <strong>Teaforthree</strong> (Mr J T McNamara) 5/1Fav<br />
2. <strong>Harry The Viking</strong> (Mr W Biddick) 7/1<br />
3. <strong>Four Commanders</strong> (Miss N Carberry) 10/1<br />
19 Ran</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>