<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="online-bets.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting | Cheltenham Festival Free Bets Offers | Online Bookmakers Guide]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cheltenham gold cup, free bets, betting offers, cheltenham festival, free bet, bookmakers, online betting, horse racing free bets, cheltenham bet, gold cup free bet, bookmaker free bets]]></keys><description><![CDATA[Free bets and bookmakers betting offers for the Cheltenham Gold Cup. Free bet guide for the Cheltenham Festival Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Festival Gold Cup Betting</h1>
<p><img align="right" src="images/bookmakers.jpg" alt="Cheltenham Betting" />With the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup </a>one of the biggest races of the National Hunt Season all the online bookmakers will be offering very good <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/promotions.html">Gold Cup free bets </a>to encourage you to open an account with the online bookmaker.</p>
<p>The average free bet offers are in the region of 25 on a cash match basis and we have a selection of the best offer available right here. How these free bets work is quite simple in that the online bookmaker will match your fist bet to the amount of your first bet with them to the maximum that they have stated in there advertising.</p>
<p>So once you have made your Cheltenham Gold Cup selection and have identified the best <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Odds </a>on our odds comparison site then you should check the Gold Cup free bet offers and the bookmaker offering he best price and the largest offer should maybe the site which gets your business.</p>
<h2>Online Bookmakers Guide</h2>
<p><img align="right" src="images/betting.jpg" alt="Cheltenham Bookmakers Guide" />Over the last few years the online betting business has grown significantly as it is a very computer friendly way of placing a bet for the consumer and cost effective also for the bookmakers.</p>
<p>All the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/opening-an-online-betting-account.html">high street bookmakers </a>have very good online sites and we have identified the very best online bookmakers for your consideration. All these sites are very reputable businesses and many will be very recognisable to you but some less so but all are worthy of your consideration.</p>
<p>All these online bookmakers will be offering a Gold Cup free horse racing bet to encourage you to open an account with them. You can get to the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/opening-an-online-betting-account.html">online bookmaker </a>of your choice by simply clicking on the links provided here and this will open up the page that will enable you to open an account with that bookmaker and simply follow the instructions and you can have an account opened in minutes.</p>]]></content><articles></articles></page>