<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="opening-an-online-betting-account.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Opening an Online Betting Account | Cheltenham Gold Cup | Free Bets | Bookmakers]]></title><keys><![CDATA[Opening an Online Betting Account, Cheltenham Gold Cup, Free Bets, Bookmakers, free bets]]></keys><description><![CDATA[How to set up and online betting account with the online bookmakers]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Opening an Online bookmaker account</h1>
<p><img alt="Bookmakers Betting Account" align="right" src="images/betting_account.jpg" />You have now made your <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup </a>selection or which to back our <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/tips.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup tips </a>and then all you need to do is decide the online bookmaker which either offers the best price about your selection or best suits your betting requirements or even offers the best <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/promotions.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup free bet</a>, and then all that's left to do is open the account.</p>
<p>Simply click on any of the links on this site for the bookmaker you have chosen and this will take you directly to that online bookmaker and from there you see the open an account button which you click on and go through the simply registration process.</p>
<h2>Paddy Power Free £100&nbsp;Cheltenham Gold Cup Bets</h2>
<p><a target="_blank" href="out.php?url=12"><img border="0" alt="Paddy Power Free Bet" align="right" src="http://www.moneta-communications.com/banners/paddypower/paddypower_125x100.gif" /></a> Paddy Power the innovative and customer friendly Irish Bookmakers are offering one of the best Free bets currently available for&nbsp;the Cheltenham Gold Cup. The company are now Irelands leading independent bookmakers are renowned for their unique betting offers that very often greatly assist existing customers, proving that it certainly pays to have an account up and running with them. The offer is £100 for new customers using their online gaming site. Just follow the prompts after clicking the link.</p>
<p><a target="_blank" href="out.php?url=12">Claim a free bet of £100 For the&nbsp;2010&nbsp;Cheltenham Gold&nbsp;Cup&nbsp;with Paddy Power</a></p>
<p>Registering with an online bookmaker is a very straightforward process and only takes a few minutes. You will be asked for some personal information such as name, age, address and a few other very simple questions for your account security. Once this is complete you will asked to lodge some funds to place your Cheltenham Gold Cup Free Bet and this can be done with either your Debit or Credit Cards.</p>
<p>Should your selection become one of the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/results.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Winners </a>you can then have your winnings sent straight back to the bank card you used when lodging your funds.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/promotions.html"><span style="font-size: larger"><u>Great Gold Cup Free Bets Available on this Site</u></span></a></p>]]></content><articles></articles></page>