<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="pandorama.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Pandorama Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 | Betting | Form | Runners]]></title><keys><![CDATA[pandorama odds, cheltenham gold cup 2012, betting, form, runners, free bets, lexus chase, noel meade]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the form and betting odds for Pandorama who is one of the leading contendersfor the Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders 2012 - Pandorama</h1>
<p>
	Pandorama is a horse that has long been thought highly over in Ireland and after winning the Lexus Chase at Leopardstown over Christmas looks to be backing those claims up this season. The Noel Meade horse will now be aimed at the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> and looks to in with a real chance if he continues to improve, and he could well turn out to be the strongest challenger at Cheltenham from Ireland. Pandorama is a multiple Grade 1 winner in Ireland including wins in the Drinmore Novice Chase at Fairyhouse last season and the Knight Frank Novice Chase at Leopardstown which was also last season.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Pandorama Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 Odds</a></p>
<p>
	Pandorama started this season in unconvincing fashion when he was pulled up at Newbury in the Hennessy Gold Cup; he was badly hampered that day and can be excused for the run. That was confirmed with his fine win in the Lexus Chase with a good field behind him including the likes of Joncol and Glencove Marina, it was the best run of his career and he looks to be improving through the season. We are likely to see Pandorama next up in the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/irish-hennessy-gold-cup.html">Irish Hennessy Gold Cup</a> and he will look to continue that fine form back at Leoparstown in February.</p>
<p>
	It is clear from his run in the Lexus that Pandorama clearly prefers some cut in the ground and that could well play against him at Cheltenham; more often than not we see the ground come up on the fast side of good for the Festival which could be a disadvantage. That being said he is an improving horse and at eight years old he looks to be at the right age for a big run at Cheltenham, on form he has something to find against the big boys here but he is entitled to step up.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>