<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="paul-nicholls-specials.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Paul Nicholls Special Bets | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2011 | Odds | Kauto Star | First Three Home]]></title><keys><![CDATA[paul nicholls special bets, cheltenham gold cup 2011, odds, kauto star, denman, free bets, champion trainer, markets, what a friend, first three home]]></keys><description><![CDATA[The Paul Nicholls Special Bets feature the different bets available for the trainer for the 2011 Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Gold Cup 2011 - Paul Nicholls Special Bets</h1>
<p>One name has dominated the Gold cup in recent years and that is Paul Nicholls and that is showing no signs of changing in 2011 with the Ditcheat trainer set&nbsp; to saddle several <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup Runners </a>once again. The last few years has seen Nicholls dominate the race with Kauto Star and Denman winning the race between them, in 2008 Nicholls had the first three home in the big race with Denman, Kauto Star and Neptune Collonges making up the places.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">2011 Cheltenham Gold Cup Odds</a></p>
<p>Many punters are predicting that could happen again in 2011 with Kauto and Denman being joined by What A Friend and they are likely to be near the front of the field while Nicholls also has several other horses who are capable of being the best of the rest. There are several special bets surrounding Paul Nicholls for the 2010 Gold Cup with punters being given the chance to have a bet on the Champion Trainer. He has a solid if unspectacular week so far at Cheltenham with Master Minded being beaten in one of the shock results of the week, what effect will that have on the Gold Cup?</p>
<h2>Potential Paul Nicholls Gold Cup Runners 2011</h2>
<ul>
    <li>Kauto Star</li>
    <li>Denman&nbsp;</li>
    <li>Tricky Trickster</li>
    <li>What A Friend</li>
    <li>Neptune Collonges</li>
</ul>
<br />]]></content><articles></articles></page>