<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="punchestowns.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Punchestowns Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2011 | Runners | Betting | Form]]></title><keys><![CDATA[punchestowns odds, cheltenham gold cup 2011, runners, betting, form, free bets, chances, henderson, cheltenham festival]]></keys><description><![CDATA[Punchestowns is one of the leading contenders for the 2011 Gold Cup at the Cheltenham Festival and includes his form and odds.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2011 - Punchestowns</h1>
<p>Punchestowns is a very interesting potential Gold cup runner this season as he continues to make progress during his career, he was a top class staying hurdler and has now moved into chasing with some good results. The horse is trained by Nicky Henderson in Lambourn and is expected to improve once again this campaign as he turns 8 years old. He has some good scalps on his record without ever having won a really big race at the Cheltenham Festival, this will be a worry for his backers this year as we approach the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> In March.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Punchestowns Cheltenham Gold Cup 2011 Odds</a></p>
<p>Punchestowns showed at the 2009 Cheltenham Festival he was a classy type when he pushed Big Buck's all the way in the World Hurdle before just coming up short, he moved into Chasing last year and had a couple of nice wins at Newbury and Sandown. We last saw him in the RSA Chase at the Festival in March, he went off well backed as favourite but was never involved after coming in lame. The injury means he can be forgiven that run and should bounce back this season, if he does continue to progress as hoped he is more than entitled to take his chance in the Gold Cup.</p>
<p>It is understood that Punchestowns will be on a path towards the Gold Cup this season so each of his runs will prove vital to his Gold Cup Odds as well as his actual participation in the big race. He could be the surprise package in the Gold Cup field this season so punters should watch his progress very closely indeed, as and when he appears we will be updating his form guide as well as his Gold Cup price.</p>
<h2>Punchestowns 2010/11 Form</h2>
<p>Awaiting form</p>]]></content><articles></articles></page>