<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="quito-de-la-roque.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Quito De La Roque Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 | Betting | Form | Festival]]></title><keys><![CDATA[quito de la roque odds, cheltenham gold cup 2013, betting, form, festival, colm murphy, guide, price, favourite, contender, market]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and form for Quito de La Roque who is featuring in the betting for the 2013 Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders 2013 - Quito De La Roque</h1>
<p>
	The Colm Murphy trained Quito de La Roque might just be the leading <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup </a>contender from Ireland heading to Cheltenham this season after a serious of good performances. Towards the end of last season Quito De La Roque really started to show some true potential as a novice Chaser with his win in the Champion Novice Chase at the Punchestown Festival the highlight.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Quito De La Roque Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 Win Odds</a></p>
<p>
	One thing we can be sure of with Quito De La Roque is that he will stay the trip at Cheltenham, he is a dour stayer and it only remains to find out if he has enough class in this company. One of his most impressive runs of this season so far was his win in the JNWine Champion Chase at Down Royal when he stayed on to claim the win in top class company. That day he looked beaten with Sizing Europe well clear but he kept plugging on up the hill to win a touch cosily in the end to see his Gold Cup price clipped.</p>
<p>
	It is clear that Quito De La Roque is an improving horse that stays well but as yet we are waiting to find out his true potential in Gold Cup company. He is clearly one to consider and it would be no surprise to see Quito in the frame at the Festival despite having plenty to find in the form book.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>