<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="sir-des-champs.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Sir Des Champs Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting 2013 | Runners | Form | Festival]]></title><keys><![CDATA[sir des champs odds, cheltenham gold cup betting 2013, trainers, form, festival, runners, willie mullins, gigginstown stud, races, contenders, season, winter, results]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the form and betting odds for Sir Des Champs who is one of the leading contenders in the betting for the 2013 Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2013 - Sir Des Champs</h1>
<p>
	We are counting down to the 2013 Cheltenham <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net">Gold Cup</a> and one of the leading contenders in the betting is the highly exciting Sir Des Champs. The Willie Mullins trained horse has won at the Cheltenham Festival for the past couple of years and connections are eager to send him over the three mile trip. In 2011 we saw Sir Des Champs win the Conditional Jockeys Hurdle at the Festival which was the first sign of his potential.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Sir Des Champs Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 Win Odds</a></p>
<p>
	The horse followed that win up with another win at the Festival in 2012 when he stormed up the hill to win the Jewson Novices Chase over 2m 5f. The Jewson win was top class as he beat a good field in what on the face of it looked like one of the highlights of the 2012 Festival. That day he clearly looked as if he had more in the tank and so far he remains unbeaten since coming over to the Mullins stable from France. At this stage it is fair to say that Sir Des Champs could be anything, he could well be the horse to give the Gigginstown team their first Gold Cup winner since War Of Attrition in 2006.</p>
<h2>
	Sir Des Champs Gold Cup 2013 Form Guide</h2>
<p>
	Sir Des Champs started his season with a second place in the John Durkan Chase behind the highly exciting Flemenstar. It is fair to say that Sir Des Champs will want further than the 2m4f trip on offer in the John Durkan and he couldn&#39;t cope with the speed and flair of Flemenstar with Sir Des Champs unable to land a blow in second.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>