<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="the-giant-bolster.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[The Giant Bolster Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting | Form Guide]]></title><keys><![CDATA[the giant bolster odds, cheltenham gold cup betting, form guide, past results, trainer, jockey, contenders]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the betting and form for The Giant Bolster who is one of the leading contenders in the betting for the Cheltenham Gold Cup.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders 2013 - The Giant Bolster</h1>
<p>
	The Giant Bolster is a fascinating betting prospect in the Gold Cup market this season and there will be plenty of punters looking to follow this horse. Last season we saw The Giant Bolster run an absolute blinder in the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> to chase Synchronised home and few would bet against him doing something similar in 2013.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Cheltenham Gold Cup Price for The Giant Bolster</a></p>
<p>
	The horse trained by David Bridgwater seems to reserve his best for Cheltenham and course form is always vital when it comes to the Gold Cup. We know he stays the trip which is much more than we can say for a number of his rivals here and his second place ahead of Long Run last season can only be described as rock solid form.</p>
<p>
	This season has been slightly disappointing for The Giant Bolster following his second place in the Gold Cup but connections remain hopeful of a big run at the Festival. We saw him finish a decent third behind Silviniaco Conti and Long Run at Haydock in the Betfair Chase back in October before he was pulled up in the King George at Kempton on heavy ground on Boxing Day.</p>
<p>
	On most of his form it is hard to give The Giant Bolster much hope in the Gold cup this season but his Cheltenham form demands he must be respected. A repeat of his run in the race last season will see him go very close indeed and that alone will ensure he is the subject of plenty of each-way punts in the build up to the race itself.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>