<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="tips.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting Tips | Free Selections From Channel Four Racing's Tom Lee]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cheltenham gold cup betting tips, cheltenham festival, odds, trends, pointers, tom lee channel four racing bets, selections]]></keys><description><![CDATA[Betting tips from Channel Four Racing's Tom Lee for the Cheltenham Gold Cup for 2014 including pointers and trends.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>2016 Gold Cup Tips</h1>

<p><img alt="Cheltenham Festival Gold Cup Tips" src="images/tips.jpg" style="float:right" />Getting a Cheltenham Gold Cup tip is something that we will be putting up closer to the event. The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup </a>is one of the more predictable of the Cheltenham Festival races as the form is well advertised prior to the event each year and the Gold Cup has been very good to favourites in recent years.</p>

<p>Part of selecting the Cheltenham Gold Cup Results is to look back on previous years results and analyse their form going into the race, a clear Gold Cup tip in recent times is that the King George winner is more than likely to run a big race in the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Betting Odds</a>.</p>

<p>Another very important Cheltenham Gold Cup tip is that you should look at selecting a horse that has course form as Imperial Commander had shown in the year's before he won the Gold Cup in 2010,,in general it is not the Gold Cup distance that can cause problems for horses but the undulations on the course often proving far more relevant. There are just those horse that prefer flat tracks and these horses sometimes do not translate their form to Cheltenham. Check out the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/form-guide.html">Cheltenham Gold Cup Form guide</a> for more information about the leading fancies in the race.</p>

<h2>Cheltenham Gold Cup Race Trends</h2>

<ul>
	<li>Six favourites have won the Gold Cup since 2000</li>
	<li>Only two horses older than 9 have won in the last 20 years</li>
	<li>Paul Nicholls has trained the Gold Cup winner four times with three different horses since 1999</li>
	<li>The biggest price Gold Cup winner this century was Lord Windermere who won at 20/1 in 2014</li>
</ul>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>