<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="trials.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Gold Cup 2014 | Trial Races | King George Chase | Form | Results]]></title><keys><![CDATA[Cheltenham Gold cup 2014, trial races, king george chase, form, denman chase, hennessy Gold Cup, long run, runners, results, lexus,]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the results of thhe trial races for the 2012 Cheltenham Gold Cup including the Hennessy Gold Cup and King George VI Chase at Kempton Park.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup 2014 - Trial Races</h1>
<p>
	The Gold Cup is quite simply the biggest race of the season as well as at the Cheltenham Festival and there is a tried and tested route for potential runners to take during the season. <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> contenders tend to have two or three runs at the most before going to Cheltenham for the big race and punters are well advised to take note of the trial races before having a bet at the Festival in March.</p>
<h2>
	Gold Cup Trial Races</h2>
<p>
	Betfair Chase</p>
<p>
	The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betfair-chase.html">Betfair Chase</a> is a great starting point for Gold Cup horses and is one that 2011 Gold Cup winner Long Run has used for the past two seasons, the race at Haydock is a good chance for the runners to get a run in early in the season in November.</p>
<ul>
	<li>
		2012 Winner<strong> - Silviniaco Conti</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>
	Hennessy Gold Cup</p>
<p>
	The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/hennessy-gold-cup.html">Hennessy Gold Cup</a> at Newbury is one of the biggest handicap races of the season and is often an ideal preparation race for the Gold Cup, it is run each November and the big field always makes it a competitive race for punters to take advantage of. Denman has used the race to start his season for much of his career while Carruthers was the winner last season and was slashed in the Gold Cup Betting as a result.</p>
<ul>
	<li>
		<strong>2012 Winner - Bobs Worth</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>
	King George VI Chase</p>
<p>
	There is no doubt that the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/king-george-vi-chase.html">King George VI Chase </a>is the most prestigious Gold Cup Trial race and falling at Christmas it is a massive race in its own right. Kauto Star has of course made the race his own winning it five times during his career while Long Run won in 2010 before going onto win the Gold Cup in the same season. The course at Kempton is a flat track so any horse that can win at Kempton and on the undulations at Cheltenham in the same season will always be considered the ultimate chaser.</p>
<ul>
	<li>
		<strong>2012 Winner - Long Run</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>
	Lexus Chase</p>
<p>
	The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/lexus-chase.html">Lexus Chase</a> is one of the big trial races in Ireland for the Cheltenham Gold Cup and it is run at Leopardstown each Christmas, there is always a good field for this one and always gives one or two Gold Cup clues. We can expect another top class race this season and it is certainly one to keep an eye on.</p>
<ul>
	<li>
		<strong>2012 Winner - Tidal Bay</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>
	Irish Hennessy Gold Cup</p>
<p>
	The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/irish-hennessy-gold-cup.html">Irish Hennessy Gold Cup</a> is of course the equivalent of the Newbury version and offers the Irish contenders another chance to find their form before heading across the sea for the Cheltenham Gold Cup. The Irish Hennessy is run at Leopardstown in February and always attracts a good field as connections looks to get a good run into their horses.</p>
<ul>
	<li>
		<strong>2013 Winner</strong> - <strong>Sir Des Champs</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>
	Denman Chase</p>
<p>
	The Denman Chase is a vital Cheltenham Gold Cup Trial as it falls just a few short weeks before the big race in February, it is the last chance for those horses who need a tune up to get ready for the Festival. <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/aon-chase.html">The Denman Chase</a> is run at Newbury over 3 miles and has attracted some great fields over the years with perhaps Kauto Star in 2007 and Denman in 2008 the most famous winners of the race in recent times.</p>
<ul>
	<li>
		<strong>2013 Winner - Silviniaco Conti</strong></li>
</ul>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>