<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="watch-live.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Cheltenham Gold Cup 2014 | Watch Live Coverage On The Internet]]></title><keys><![CDATA[cheltenham gold cup 2014, watch live coverage, internet, festival, lladbrokes, paddy power, vc bet, streaming, channel 4, bookmakers]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the information on how to watch the 2014 Cheltenham Gold Cup including on the TV and on the Internet.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Watch the Cheltenham Gold Cup 2014 Live</h1>
<p>
	The <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> is one of the biggest races of the season and with it being held on a Friday many punters and fans are forced to find another way of watching the big race, thankfully these days that is no longer a problem with several of the major bookmakers offering streaming of the race. There is of course live TV coverage throughout the week on Channel 4 in the UK but for those of you away from the TV and in the office the online bookmakers are the best bet.</p>
<p>
	Any punters that open an account and have a bet on the Gold Cup or any of the races at the Cheltenham Festival will have access to live streaming of the race as it happens. This means that no matter where you are, as long as you have access to the internet on your computer, ipad or phone you will be able to cheer your horse on. The gold Cup is of course raced on a Friday so there will be thousands of punters wanting to catch the action from the office, this is where the bookmakers come in and it is well worth opening an account with one of the firms to follow a bet live.</p>
<h2>
	Ladbrokes</h2>
<p>
	One of the major bookmakers to offer this service is <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/out.php?url=16" target="_new">Ladbrokes</a>, they will offer punters the free streaming once they have opened an account and placed a bet on the race in question. Ladbrokes TV is an excellent service and offers punters exactly what they are looking for throughout the Cheltenham Festival with the Gold Cup the highlight of the week on Friday afternoon.</p>
<h2>
	VC Bet</h2>
<p>
	Victor Chandler are another one of the major online bookmakers and they too offer an excellent streaming service for punters who have an account with them and have had a bet on the particular race in question. A minimum bet is required by <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/out.php?url=10" target="_new">VC Bet</a> and after that the service is excellent so Victor Chandler customers can follow the racing where ever they may be with the Gold Cup the feature race of the week at the Cheltenham Festival.</p>
<p>
	It is an excellent way to follow your bet as well as catching one of the best races of the season as it happens, so whether you are at home in front of the TV or at work in front the PC you will not miss a second of the 2014 Gold Cup.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>