<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="weird-al.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[Weird Al Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup Odds 2012 | Form | Tips | Bets]]></title><keys><![CDATA[weird al odds, cheltenham gold cup odds 2012, form, tips, runners, bets, specials, donald mccain jnr, ]]></keys><description><![CDATA[All the form and betting for Weird Al who is one of the leading contenders in the Cheltenham Gold cup betting.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Contenders 2012 - Weird Al</h1>
<p>
	Weird Al has proven himself a talented chaser over the past couple of years and after joining trainer Donald McCain Jnr over the Summer he now looks a real <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/">Gold Cup</a> contender. He has been mixing it with the very best for some time now and his win in the Charlie Hall Chase at the start of the season is being seen as a career best run as he finished ahead of the likes of Time For Rupert and Nacarat.</p>
<p>
	<a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Latest Weird Al Cheltenham Gold Cup 2012 Win Odds</a></p>
<p>
	We saw Weird Al run in the Gold last season but he never really travelled which was something of a surprise. It was clear that Weird Al was nowhere near his best as he was pulled up and has to be given another chance this year having moved stables from Ian Williams over the summer. Donald McCain is one of the top class trainers in the country at the moment and Weird Al is sure to improve for his move to the north of England stable.</p>
<p>
	Weird Al followed up his win in the Charlie Hall Chase with another decent run in the Betfair Chase last time out in tougher company. That day at Haydock he could only finish third behind a great run from Kauto Star and Long Run who came in second in what looked like a top class Gold Cup Trial. Weird Al ran a good race to keep plugging on to finish third behind two horses of the very highest quality and that proves he is more than capable of mixing it at the <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/cheltenham-festival.html">Cheltenham Festival</a> in March.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>