<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?><page name="what-a-friend.html"><metas><title><![CDATA[What A Friend Odds | Cheltenham Gold Cup 2013 | Runners | Betting | Form | Chances]]></title><keys><![CDATA[what a friend odds, cheltenham gold cup 2013, runners, betting, form, chances, free bets, nicholls, sir alex ferguson, record, winner, owner, cheltennham festival]]></keys><description><![CDATA[What a Friend is one of the leading contendrs in the betting for the 2013 Cheltenham Gold Cup and features his form latest odds.]]></description></metas><content><![CDATA[<h1>
	Cheltenham Gold Cup Runners 2013 - What A Friend</h1>
<p>
	What A Friend is one of the new breed of potential Gold Cup horses this season and he is a hugely interesting contender for punters to consider for the big race, he is another one from the Paul Nicholls yard and they think a lot of the Sir Alex Ferguson owned horse. What A Friend has been improving steadily for the past couple of years and now looks ready to challenge the stable dominance of Kauto Star and Long Run.</p>
<p>
	2009/10 really was a breakthrough season for What A Friend as he picked up two Group 1 victories, he won the Lexus Chase at Leopardstown at Christmas beating the likes of Joncol and Cooldine with ease before winning the Totesport Bowl at Aintree. That was the race that saw Imperial Commander take a fall but What A Friend was hugely impressive that day and looked the real deal. He is now 9-years-old so looks to be the perfect age for a big run at the Cheltenham Festival, he may not be as big a name as his stable mates just yet but punters should write him off at their peril.</p>
<p>
	What A Friend is expected to start off his season with a run in the Betfair Chase at Haydock in November, this will see him come up against Imperial Commander in an intriguing early season clash. We will find out plenty about both horses at Haydock while also appreciating that both will come on for the run, if What A Friend can push the Gold Cup winner close here or even beat him we will see his <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net/betting-odds.html">Gold Cup Odds</a> slashed.</p>
<p>
	What A Friend will need to continue his improvement this season but there is no questioning his class at this stage, he will stay the trip with no problems and could prove the value in the ante-post <a href="http://www.cheltenham-goldcup.net">Cheltenham Gold Cup</a> market.</p>
]]></content><articles></articles></page>